Welcome all of you to Chitresh S KB News Helper Channel.
In this video, we are going to
talk about ICICI LB General
Insurance Company Limited
which has published its Quarter 4
numbers today.  So
only the announcement of financial results is being
seen from the company.
Apart from this, there is
a final dividend announcement which is of
₹7 per equity share.
Apart from this, we are
not getting to see any such announcement regarding bonus split.
So let us see how the financial results of
Quarter 4 of ICICI LBAT General Insurance Company Limited
were.
We will discuss all the figures in these lax in quarters.
Quarter four data is seen
in the first row, quarter three data is seen
in the second row and last year quarter four
data is seen in the third row.
So first of all let us talk about the total income
which was Rs
56000 535 crores last year, this time it has increased to Rs
58517 crores.  And in the last quarter the
income was Rs 5882.83 crore.  He fell short this time.
Came down to Rs 58517 crore.  So on yearly basis the
company's income seems to be increasing.
But income seems to be decreasing on a quarterly basis.  Then next let's
talk
about total expenses.  The
expenses which were Rs 46380 crore last year, have increased to Rs
543525 crore this time.  And in the last quarter there were
expenses of Rs 59747 crore.  This time it
increased
to Rs 543525 crore.  So,
we are
seeing the profit expenses of the company increasing both yearly and quarterly.  Then
next let's talk
about profit and loss after tax
which was Rs
51950 crore profit last year.
This time it reduced to Rs 5959 crore.  And
in the last quarter there was a
profit of Rs 72438 crore.  This time it reduced
to Rs 5959 crore.  So,
we are seeing the company's profits decreasing both yearly and quarterly.  Then
next let's talk
about EPS, which was 10.55 last year,
this time it has come down to 10.29.  And
in the last quarter, the EPS was 14.63, which this time
reduced to 10.29.  So,
we are seeing the company's EPS decreasing both yearly and quarterly.  Then next let's
talk about NPA ratios.  So that's what
we're getting to see Neil.  Along with
this, if you people liked this video of mine, then
like, share and subscribe to our channel and
definitely press the bell icon button so that
you keep getting notifications of our every video from time
to time.  So see you
in the next video.